tippfm.com 2018-01-29

# Privacy Policy - Tipp FM

#### Privacy Policy

At Tipp FM we understand that privacy is an important issue for visitors to www.tippfm.com and its related domains. The following information is designed to help visitors understand what information we collect from our site, and how we handle and use the information thereafter.

* * *

**Information collection and use:**

Tipp FM is the sole owner of any information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Clare FM may collect information from our users at several different points on our website.

* * *

**General enquiries:**

If a user contacts Tipp FM with a general enquiry, the user may need to provide Tipp FM with personal information (for example contact details). Tipp FM will use this personal information to respond to the enquiry and track further correspondence. Personal information collected is not used for any other purpose.

* * *

**Cookies:**

Cookies are small text files that a site transfers to a visitor’s hard disk or browser for added functionality or for tracking site usage. In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, Tipp FM may use cookies to determine the path users take on our site and to identify repeat visitors of our site. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person’s name or e-mail address.

* * *

**External links:**

The Tipp FM website may contain links to other sites. Please take note that Tipp FM is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

* * *

**Changes to Tipp  FM privacy policy:**

Tipp FM from time to time, make changes to this policy. We recommend that users of this site re-visit this privacy policy on occasion to learn of new privacy practices or changes to our policy

* * *

**Copyright:**

All content on our website is copyright © to Tipp FM. Use of content/images/text within this site must not be reproduced or copied without the expressed written consent of Tipp FM.
